(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
#ひろがるホロライブDAY1
開演までしばらくお待ちください
#BrightParadeHololiveDAY1
Please wait a moment until the show starts.
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023
グッズラインナップ紹介
Goods Lineup Introduction
商品ラインナップ！
3Dアクリルスタンド ブライト衣装Ver. 他
Product Lineup!
3D Acrylic Stand (Bright Costume Ver.) and others
商品ラインナップ！
ホロスターズ / ホロスターズEN グッズ
Product Lineup!
Holostars / Holostars EN Goods
商品ラインナップ！
hololive production Art Collection
Product Lineup!
ホロライブ事務所グッズ
ポストカードスタンド / IDカードホルダー 他
hololive Office Goods
Postcard Stand / ID Card Holder and others
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE グッズ
ロゴTシャツ / クリアカードセット 他
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE Goods
Logo T-shirt / Clear Card Set and others
マンガート ビームス コラボグッズ
MANGART BEAMS produce T-shirts
MANGART BEAMS Collaboration Goods
holo*27 コラボグッズ
アクリルスタンド / ランダム缶バッジ
holo*27 Collaboration Goods
Acrylic Stand / Random Badges
BUSHIROAD グッズ
アクリルミラー / ブースターパック Vol.2
BUSHIROAD Goods
Acrylic Mirror / Booster Pack Vol.2
GOOD SMILE COMPANY グッズ
ホロライブ ねんどろいどぷらす アクリルスタンド
GOOD SMILE COMPANY Goods
hololive Nendoroid Plus Acrylic Stands
hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade
OFFICIAL ITEMS
hololive 4th fes.
PENLIGHT COLORS
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 / hololive 4th fes.
デジタルメッセージボード
Digital Message Board
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 Our Bright Parade
デジタルメッセージボード
Digital Message Board
Woah woah woah...
デジタルメッセージボード
Digital Message Board
グッズラインナップ紹介
Goods Lineup Introduction
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ
Weiß Schwarz
ホロライブプロダクションが またまたカードに大集合！
Hololive Production characters are gathered on cards once again!
広がるヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Expanding Weiss Schwarz!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2
Booster Pack: hololive production Vol.2
3月24日(金) 発売！
On sale March 24th (Fri)!
ブシロード
Bushiroad
hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade x JOYSOUND
スペシャルコラボレーション
Special Collaboration
2023年5月28日(日)まで
全国の対象カラオケ店で実施中！
Through Sunday, May 28, 2023
Now underway at participating karaoke shops nationwide!
過去ライブの配信や豪華賞品が当たるキャンペーンなど
他にも企画が盛りだくさん！詳しくは みるハコ
Past live distribution, campaigns to win prizes,
and more! For details, check Miru Hako.
吐く息の白さも分ければ 最高の冬が逃げ出すほどに
If we share even the whiteness of our breath, the best winter will run away
だって全力になっちゃって もう止められないね 待って！
Because I'm giving it my all, I can't be stopped anymore, wait!
どうしちゃったの？絶対好き、絶対好き、絶対好きでしょ
What's wrong? You definitely like it, definitely like it, definitely like it, right?
Are you embarrassed? Now you're blushing somehow
グッズラインナップ紹介
Goods Lineup Introduction
オンライン通販も開始！
Online sales have also started!
hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade OFFICIAL ITEMS
Tシャツ White / Tシャツ Black ¥3,300
T-shirt White / T-shirt Black ¥3,300
ペンライト ¥4,400
Penlight ¥4,400
マフラータオル ¥2,200
Muffler Towel ¥2,200
PENLIGHT COLORS
デジタルメッセージボード
Digital Message Board
ライブ楽しみにしてます！！
I'm looking forward to the live!!
全力で応援してます！
I'm supporting you with all my might!
ホロライブに出会えて毎日が楽しいです！
Since I found hololive, every day is fun!
4th fes 開催おめでとう！
Congratulations on the 4th fes!
ホロライブに出会えてよかった！
I'm so glad I found hololive!
最高のステージをありがとう！
Thank you for the best stage!
これからもずっと応援し続けます！
I'll continue to support you forever!
ひろがるホロライブ！
Expanding hololive!
ライブ最高！！
The live is the best!!
デジタルメッセージボード
Digital Message Board
hololive stage DAY1
#ひろがるホロライブDAY1
開演までしばらくお待ちください
hololive stage DAY1
#HologirlsSpreadDAY1
Please wait a while until the performance starts.
グッズラインナップ紹介
Goods Lineup Introduction
オンライン通販も開始！
Online sales have also started!
商品ラインナップ！
Product Lineup!
ホロスターズ 商品ラインナップ！
HOLOSTARS Product Lineup!
商品ラインナップ！
Product Lineup!
ホロライブ事務所グッズ
hololive Office Goods
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE グッズ
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE Goods
マンガアートビームス コラボグッズ
MANGART BEAMS Collaboration Goods
holo*27 コラボグッズ
holo*27 Collaboration Goods
BUSHIROAD グッズ
BUSHIROAD Goods
GOOD SMILE COMPANY グッズ
GOOD SMILE COMPANY Goods
商品ラインナップ!
Product Lineup!
ホロライブ ねんどろいどぷらす アクリルスタンド
hololive Nendoroid Plus Acrylic Stand
OFFICIAL ITEMS
ペンライト、Tシャツ、マフラータオル
Penlight, T-shirt, Muffler Towel
PENLIGHT COLORS
デジタルメッセージボード
Digital Message Board
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiβ Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションがまたまたカードに！
hololive production is back on cards again!
大集合！
Everyone, gather 'round!
広がるヴァイスシュヴァルツ
Expanding Weiss Schwarz
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2
Booster Pack: Hololive Production Vol.2
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
Our Bright Parade x JOYSOUND スペシャルコラボレーション
Our Bright Parade x JOYSOUND Special Collaboration
コラボドリンクをご注文の方に、オリジナルコースタープレゼント！
Order a collaboration drink and get an original coaster!
ハイライトもすべて奪い去るヴァーチャルあけ
Stealing all the highlights, a Virtual dawn
なんて全開　あんなっちゃってもうやめてしたーい
Full throttle! Even if I end up like that, I want to stop!
どうしちゃったの　絶対絶対絶対好きでしょ
What's wrong? You definitely, definitely, definitely love it.
Are you embarrassed now? Or blushing somehow?
hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 グッズラインナップ紹介
hololive SUPER EXPO 2023 Merchandise Lineup Introduction
商品ラインナップ！
Product Lineup!
ホロライブ事務所グッズ
hololive Office Merchandise
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE グッズ
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE Merchandise
マンカート ビームス コラボグッズ
MANGART BEAMS Collaboration Merchandise
holo*27 コラボグッズ
holo*27 Collaboration Merchandise
BUSHIROAD グッズ
BUSHIROAD Merchandise
GOOD SMILE COMPANY グッズ
GOOD SMILE COMPANY Merchandise
Official Items
PENLIGHT COLORS
デジタルメッセージボード
Digital Message Board
グッズラインナップ紹介
Goods Lineup Introduction
オンライン通販も開始！
Online sales have also started!
商品ラインナップ！
Product Lineup!
ホロライブ事務所グッズ
hololive Office Goods
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE グッズ
HOLOLIVE ALTERNATIVE Goods
マンガアートビームス コラボグッズ
MANGART BEAMS Collaboration Goods
holo*27 コラボグッズ
holo*27 Collaboration Goods
BUSHIROAD グッズ
BUSHIROAD Goods
GOOD SMILE COMPANY グッズ
GOOD SMILE COMPANY Goods
hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade
OFFICIAL ITEMS
PENLIGHT COLORS
デジタルメッセージボード
DIGITAL MESSAGE BOARD
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiß Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションがまたまたカードに大集合！
Hololive Production is back again in a big gathering on cards!
広がるヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Expanding Weiß Schwarz!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2
Booster Pack Hololive Production Vol.2
3月24日(金)発売
On sale March 24th (Fri)
ブシロード
Bushiroad
JOYSOUND スペシャルコラボレーション
JOYSOUND Special Collaboration
holo*27 NOW ON SALE!
スバルー！
Subaru!
Koyoris / Koyori / FAMS
こよりー！
Koyori!
こより / スーパー / ダイスキ
大好き / しゅば / エモ
Koyori / Super / I love you
I love you / Shuba / Emo
こよりちゃん！スバルちゃん！
Koyori-chan! Subaru-chan!
しゅば
Shuba
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
ときのそら
Tokino Sora
ロボ子さん
Robocosan
AZKi
さくらみこ
Sakura Miko
夜空メル
Yozora Mel
赤井はあと
Akai Haato
癒月ちょこ
Yuzuki Choco
大空スバル
Oozora Subaru
不知火フレア
Shiranui Flare
白銀ノエル
Shirogane Noel
角巻わため
Tsunomaki Watame
姫森ルーナ
Himemori Luna
尾丸ポルカ
Omaru Polka
ラプラス・ダークネス
La+ Darknesss
鷹嶺ルイ
Takane Lui
博衣こより
Hakui Koyori
沙花叉クロヱ
Sakamata Chloe
風真いろは
Kazama Iroha
アユンダ・リス
Ayunda Risu
アイラニ・イオフィフティーン
Airani Iofifteen
クレイジー・オリー
Kureiji Ollie
小鳥遊キアラ
Takanashi Kiara
一伊那爾栖
Ninomae Ina'nis
ワトソン・アメリア
Watson Amelia
七詩ムメイ
Nanashi Mumei
10... 9... 8... 7... 6...
5... 4... 3... 2... 1
hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our fresh excitement resonate
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
The best of times with the best of friends
煌めきに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
Yeah!
覚えてるかな？
Do you remember?
最初の歌
The first song
懐かしいね
So nostalgic, isn't it?
重なった声が
Our overlapping voices...
震えていた
...were trembling
眩しい
Dazzling
あの日から続く未来は
The future that has continued since that day
みんなと掴んだ情熱
The passion we grasped together
もっともっともっともっと
More and more and more and more
加速するハート
My heart accelerates
一緒に行こう どこまでも
Let's go together, no matter how far
会いに行く 準備はOK?
I'm coming to see you, ready?
開け夢の扉を
Open the door to our dreams
1 2 3
キラメキライダー!
Kirameki Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make this fresh heartbeat resound
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
The best time, with the best friends
ここにいるよ
I am here
見つけてくれたから
Because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to see you
みんなで歌おう
Let's all sing together
終わらないメロディ
A never-ending melody
きらめきに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
Yeah!
届いてるかな
I wonder if it's reaching you
私の声
My voice
届けたいのは
What I want to deliver
君に笑顔 (Your Smile)
Is a smile to you (Your Smile)
理想の交差
Crossing ideals
増やして
Increasing them
みんなと同じ眼差しで
With the same look in our eyes
ギュッギュッギュッギュッと
Tightly, tightly
全て抱きしめて
Hugging everything
一緒に行こう どこまでも
Let's go together, no matter how far
会いに行く 準備はOK?
I'm coming to see you, ready?
進め 希望の道を
Go forward on the path of hope
1 2 3 キラメキライダー!
1 2 3 Kirameki Rider!
好きな気持ちカラフルに奏でたみんな
Everyone performed these feelings of love colorfully
最高の場所 最高の仲間と
The best place, with the best friends
ここにいるよ 幻なんかじゃない
I am here, it's not an illusion
君の心が
So that your heart
幸せに染まるように
Is dyed in happiness
重ねていくハーモニー
Layering this harmony
きらめき纏って
Clad in sparkle
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep singing
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep dancing
そんな願いは
Such a wish
ワガママもいいでしょ?
It's okay to be selfish, right?
だって楽しすぎて
Because it's too much fun
もう止まらない
I can't stop anymore
輝くステージで
On this shining stage
もっともっと
More and more
お願い ずっと!
Please, forever!
Yeah!
嬉しい 楽しい 愛おしいだけじゃ 語れない
Just happy, fun, and dear isn't enough to describe it
今も今も悩みはあるけど
Even now, there are worries, but
ここにいるよ 私ここにいるよ
I am here, I am right here
君と同じ世界を
Looking at the same world
見つめて
As you
1 2 3
キラメキライダー!
Kirameki Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make this fresh heartbeat resound
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
The best time, with the best friends
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I am here, because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to see you
みんなで歌おう
Let's all sing together
せーの!
One, two!
終わらないメロディ
A never-ending melody
きらめきに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
きらめき纏って
Clad in sparkle
Yeah!
Even if find me, you happy all day?
真実をかけても 一日中幸せなんだってさ!
They say even if truth is on the line, you're happy all day!
Most family leave you alone for a while.
この前は放置して ひとりぼっちにしたの。
The other day, I left you alone and ignored you.
Even more you ask me to stop in this place.
それでも、ねだり顔して 止めてほしいくせに。
Even so, you have that begging look, wanting me to stop.
How can my life be like this disgusting life?
どうしてこんな 酷い人生になるのかしら
I wonder how my life ended up so terrible.
みんな、ぶち上がっていけー!
Everyone, let's get fired up!
Even if I sneeze, I'm happy all day!
Last time you leave her alone for a while
Even more you ask me to slap your face
How can it be would be like this disgusting life
Don't you want step on me? In my bath water?
Are you really falling to the funky sweet babe?
Open your mouth, in bath water. Step in you and kick you harder. Give me your heart over and over me.
Am I so mean to you? I'm a baka.
Am I so mean to you? I'm a fool.
Don't you hate me, I won't let go of you anyway so.
Don't you look at me, that is no actually.
Because I think you are sweet, please forgive me.
I'm just kidding, hit me! Step on my cutest chubby belly
and play with me, I can be to give you more and more a lot of love.
Whenever I'm lonely, but your voice makes me happy and smile.
This world for just you and me, I'm here always.
Where is your place? Like Wonderland.
It would be looks like underground.
They always throw them far away.
Come here from before outside.
When you are hiding by alone.
We will be together, time of wonderful.
Stay and who you want to be, come alive.
Follow our highway, when I must smile with you
and believe hopping popping.
When you cry in my happy story and stay step by step.
When I'm mad and obsessed, and they will be out of bits.
Starting of the wonderland from my power Wonderland!
まじ最高ー！
This is the best!
まだまだいけるよなー！
You guys can still go, right?!
もっと！もっと！盛り上がってけー！
More! More! Let's get hyped!
Don't you want step on me? In my bath water?
Are you really falling to the funky sweet babe?
Open your mouth, in bath water. Step in you and kick you harder. Give me your heart over and over me.
Open your mouth, in bath water. Step in you and kick you harder. Give me your heart, always be with me.
こよりにむちゅーからちゅっとしてまえ
Be in love with Koyori and give me a kiss.
わーお！
Wow!
ホロライブサンキュー！
Hololive, thank you!
元気ですかー！
How are you all doing?!
一緒に、わーおわーお盛り上がってねー！
Let's get hyped together, wow wow!
絶対無理よ！
It's absolutely impossible!
待って待って、不意打ちだし。だってだって、不安になるし。
Wait, wait, it's so sudden. Because, because, I get anxious.
全然嘘つけないし。だってだって、バカ正直だし。
I can't tell a lie at all. Because, because, I'm foolishly honest.
正真正銘、きっと僕次第だ。
Truly, it must be up to me.
ビターギブアップなんて言わないんだから。
I won't say things like "bitter give up".
じっとしてらんないし。だってだって、動いちゃうし。
I can't stay still. Because, because, I just keep moving.
ワン・ツー・ステップでドンドン進めば、夢の式溶けちゃうの。
If I keep moving forward with a one-two step, the dream formula will melt away.
なりたい僕を。君が好きな僕を。ちゃんと余りなく見せたいな。
The "me" I want to be. The "me" that you like. I want to show it all to you properly.
あ・ちゃ・ちゃ、びっくりするほどできないじゃん。
Oh no, I can't do it at all, it's surprising.
間違って悩んだりばっかじゃん。
I'm always making mistakes and worrying.
手掛かりを君に見つけて欲しくて、僕は君に向き合いたい、だったならハッピー。
I want you to find the clues, I want to face you, if so I'd be happy.
わーおわーお、泣いてないで愛して嫉嫉して。
Wow wow, don't cry, just love me and be jealous.
わーおわーお、ダメな僕のこと覚えておいて。
Wow wow, remember even the bad parts of me.
こよりにむちゅーからちゅっとしてまえ！
Be in love with Koyori and give me a kiss!
問答しようとか何思っちゃって沈んだり。
What was I thinking, trying to argue and feeling down.
案外いけるかも、ふわり浮かんじゃってバタ足。
Maybe I can actually do it, floating up and fluttering my legs.
ぐったりがやめられない。お座りしてそれなんだっけ。
I can't stop feeling exhausted. What was that thing I did when sitting down?
ぴったりが止められない。また歩いて壁にあたるの。
I can't stop being a perfect fit. Walking again and hitting a wall.
ワン・ツー・ステップ、深呼吸してるの。やめてハイ、勘違いで。
One-two step, I'm taking a deep breath. Stop it, yes, it's just a misunderstanding.
欲しがる君と愛しすぎの僕とで、もっといける気がしています。
Between the wanting you and the overly-loving me, I feel like we can go even further.
あ・ちゃ・ちゃ、びっくりするほどできないじゃん。間違って悩んだりばっかじゃん。
Oh no, I can't do it at all, it's surprising. I'm always making mistakes and worrying.
手掛かりを君に見つけて欲しくて、僕は君に向き合いたい、だったならハッピー。
I want you to find the clues, I want to face you, if so I'd be happy.
だってやっぱり一人じゃだめだって、集まって合図して歌えば、ほら一等星。
Because after all, I can't do it alone, but if we gather and sing on cue, look, we're a first-magnitude star.
...ても言えぬ お帰りに
...but I can't even say "Welcome home."
どっと沸き立つ
A sudden roar of excitement.
隠したい 隠したいんじゃ I inza HAPPY
I want to hide it, I want to hide it, I'm in the HAPPY.
会いてぇ 会いてぇ 愛してぇ 死ぬっぺ
I want to see you, I want to see you, I love you, I'm gonna die!
ダメな僕を どーんと覚えておいて
Please remember the useless me forever.
目先 キラキラ シット ぼちぼちだ
Sparkling before my eyes, shit, it's so-so.
ギブアップなんて言わないんだぜ
I'm not gonna say "I give up!"
本命 メラメラ ぶっちぎる次第で
Burning with my true love, I'm gonna pull ahead!
破裂に 希望 痛い 万歳!
Bursting with hope, it hurts, hurrah!
君と どろどろ ずっとしちゃって
Getting all messy with you forever...
I inza HAPPY
I'm in the HAPPY.
凛々 凛々 高鳴る 鼓動が Beat it
Rin-rin, rin-rin, my heart is pounding, beat it!
期待を もっと感じて
Feel the expectations even more.
みんな盛り上がってる?
Is everyone excited?
もっと気分上げてけ!
Keep pumping up the mood!
上々 もっと Enjoy! 縁起がいいですね
Fantastic, enjoy even more! This is good luck, isn't it?
常勝 気分も 絶好 ホームラン
Always winning, feeling great, it's a home run!
団長 真の才能 階級は王
The captain's true talent is at the level of a king!
見せてあげる ラブリーパーティー
I'll show you a lovely party!
るんるん るんるん 巻き起こる 言霊タイフーン
Run-run, run-run, causing a spirit of words typhoon!
もっと Happy どこまでも どこまでもいっちゃうよ
More happy, I'll go on and on!
そうだろう こうなろう ときめき太郎
That's right, let's be like that, Tokimeki-taro!
ららら ハッピー いかがでしょうか?
La-la-la happy, how about that?
ちょっとビビッと感じたら
If you feel a little spark...
止めらんない 止めらんないくらい 胸のドキドキ ローキー
I can't stop, I can't stop, my heart is pounding, lowkey.
一周回って現在進行形
Coming full circle, currently in progress.
ぐるぐる 追いかけっこ
Round and round, playing tag.
あらららら あらららら
A-ra-ra-ra-ra, a-ra-ra-ra-ra.
このまま行くよ
I'm going to keep going like this.
凛々 凛々 高鳴る 鼓動が Beat it
Rin-rin, rin-rin, my heart is pounding, beat it!
期待を もっと感じて
Feel the expectations even more.
Jumping Jumping
熱狂 じゃあね
Enthusiasm, see ya!
お散歩気分 新世代ライブ
Feeling like a walk, new generation live!
色とりどりは 認めません
I won't accept various colors.
地上最高の言葉も言った
I also said the best words on earth.
言えない言葉を 並べる
I'll line up words I can't say.
ずっと見てて リリカルモンスター・ノエル
Keep watching me, Lyrical Monster Noel!
リンドン
Ring Dong
真っ向 かますよ ぶるぶる
Going head-on, shivering...
もっと騒げ Hands up! ぶるぶる
Make more noise, hands up! Shivering...
トークだけじゃないぜ このピンポン
It's not just talking, this "ping-pong"!
夢てろ ビート 有頂天
Dreaming beat, in seventh heaven.
上げれば 上げれば テンポ よく 文句ないタイフーン
If you raise it, if you raise it, the tempo's good, a perfect typhoon!
やっぱ Crazy バシバシバシバシ叩いちゃうよ
As expected, crazy, I'm gonna hit it hard!
Give me your love Give me your love ゆるくラップさ おざわりいかがでしょうか?
Give me your love, give me your love. A casual rap, how about a "sit"?
もっとビビッと感じてよ
Feel the spark even more.
やめらんない 目を離せない 君のハッシュタグ 吐く
I can't stop, I can't take my eyes off, breathing out your hashtag.
もう一回回って 絶好調
Spinning one more time, in top form!
伸び伸び いつも通り
Relaxed, as usual.
あらららら あらららら
A-ra-ra-ra-ra, a-ra-ra-ra-ra.
このまま行くよ
I'm going to keep going like this.
凛々 凛々 ようやく 100%
Rin-rin, rin-rin, finally 100%!
想像以上の 正体 スルーするから
Because I'll ignore your true identity, which is beyond imagination.
バンビー バンビー 来たもん勝ち
Bambi, Bambi, first come, first served!
表情しない 恥も外聞も
No expression, no shame or concern for reputation.
猛毒 なんかではありません
It's not some kind of deadly poison.
空前絶後の言葉を放っちゃう
I'm going to unleash words that are unprecedented!
Guess or Yes 何でもオーライ
Guess or yes, anything is all right!
一緒に進んでいきなさい 目覚めし
Keep moving forward together, awaken.
人と違う時もあるよ
There are times when you're different from others.
そこが いいところ
That's what's good about it.
どんな日も 笑顔にするから
Because I'll make you smile no matter what day it is.
どんどん笑って 相乗効果
Laugh more and more, creating a synergy!
ニコニコ 100万点
A smile worth a million points.
あらららら ラブ & ピース
A-ra-ra-ra-ra, love and peace.
リンリン リンリン みんななら
Ring-ring, ring-ring, if it's all of you...
リンリン リンリン できるはずさ
Ring-ring, ring-ring, you should be able to do it!
リンリン リンリン 聞かせて
Ring-ring, ring-ring, let me hear you.
リンリン と大きな声で
With a loud "Ring-ring"!
凛々 凛々 高鳴る 鼓動が Beat it
Rin-rin, rin-rin, my heart is pounding, beat it!
期待を もっと感じて
Feel the expectations even more.
Jumping Jumping
一声 おじゃみ
A single voice, "ojami".
緩やかな ハッピー メッセージ
A gentle, happy message.
色とりどりは 認めません
I won't accept various colors.
地上最高の団長だから
Because I'm the best captain on earth.
真っ直ぐ進む 一緒に進もう
Moving straight forward, let's move forward together.
リリカルモンスター 目覚めし
Lyrical Monster, awaken.
リリカルモンスターフリー
Lyrical Monster free!
イェー!
Yee!
凛々 凛々
Rin-rin, rin-rin.
見落とさないで
Don't overlook it.
本気のサイン
A sign of being serious.
全てぶつかっていって
Go and crash into everything.
私ってば全部わかっちゃう。なんたって天才だから！
I know everything. After all, I'm a genius!
何見てたか当てたげようか。あそこの可愛い子。
Let me guess what you were looking at. That cute girl over there.
ねぇ一体どういうつもり？分かるんだよそういうのって。
Hey, what exactly is your intention? I can tell those things.
天才なんかじゃなくたって、見てるんだよずっと。
Even if I weren't a genius, I've been watching you all along.
冷めたいくらい様だ足りない。
It's so cold, it's not enough.
そんなことばかり言ってたら、どっか行っちゃうからね。
If you keep saying things like that, I'm going to go somewhere else.
冷めたい夢を見ていたい。
I want to have a cold dream.
あとで泣いたって、知らないんだから！
I won't care even if you cry later!
結んでみれば 赤い糸。
If we tie it, it's a red thread of fate.
遊び尽くして テンプテーション。
Playing to my heart's content, temptation.
惑わすグラデ 繋がった。
A confusing gradation, we're connected.
I'm a caramel devil 欲しがってるわ。
I'm a caramel devil, I'm wanting you.
見惚れてしまえ最高！
Be mesmerized, it's the best!
愛してみて。
Try to love me.
頬を振れるぐらい焦がしてよ。
Burn me so much it touches my cheeks.
La la la... 甘い媚薬さ。
La la la... It's a sweet aphrodisiac.
もっと離さないで。
Don't let go anymore.
欲しなさい、キャラメル・デビルで。
Want it, with the Caramel Devil.
君の瞳奪っちゃうから。
Because I'll steal your eyes.
私ってば何でもできちゃう。なんたって天才だから！
I can do anything. After all, I'm a genius!
どこにいるか言ったげようか。君の後ろ！
Shall I tell you where I am? Behind you!
ほらやっぱり照れてんじゃん！門外漢とか嘘ばっか。
Look, you're blushing after all! Saying you're an outsider is all lies.
反省のしなよ、復習してよ。One Two!
Reflect on it, review it. One Two!
冷めたいくらい様だ足りない。
It's so cold, it's not enough.
ちょっと目離すとこれなんだから。聞いてんの？
This is what happens when I take my eyes off you for a bit. Are you listening?
溶けない魔法かけられてた。
I was under an undissolvable spell.
控えめなんてわからないの。
I don't know what being modest is.
渡し合いなら 真っ赤一地。
If we're exchanging, it's all deep red.
遊び尽くして 勘違いめ。
Playing to my heart's content, a misunderstanding.
狂っちゃうぐらい 君と痛い。
I want to be with you so much I go crazy.
I'm a caramel devil 手の震え。
I'm a caramel devil, my hands are shaking.
欲しがってるわ見惚れてしまえ。
I'm wanting you, be mesmerized.
こっち見て。
Look this way.
ポニー垂れるぐらい焦がしてよ。
Burn me so much my ponytail droops.
世界中なら La la la... 虜にしちゃう。
If it's the whole world, La la la... I'll captivate them.
もっと離さないで。
Don't let go anymore.
欲しなさい、キャラメル・デビルで。
Want it, with the Caramel Devil.
君の瞳奪っちゃうから。
Because I'll steal your eyes.
わかってるよ。君じゃなきゃ...
I know. If it's not you...
ダメ。その笑顔がいいんだよね。
No. That smile is what I like.
I'm a caramel devil 欲しがってるわ。
I'm a caramel devil, I'm wanting you.
見惚れてしまえ最高！
Be mesmerized, it's the best!
愛してみて。
Try to love me.
頬を振れるぐらい焦がしてよ。
Burn me so much it touches my cheeks.
La la la... 虜にしちゃう。
La la la... I'll captivate you.
もっと離さないで。
Don't let go anymore.
欲しなさい、キャラメル・デビルで。
Want it, with the Caramel Devil.
君の瞳奪っちゃうから。
Because I'll steal your eyes.
ほろ苦い甘い。
Bittersweet.
まだまだ甘い。
It's still sweet.
くっついて離れない。
Sticking together and not letting go.
メルのことちゃんと見てくれてた？
Were you watching Mel properly?
えへへ、ありがとう。これからもずっとそばにいてね！
Ehehe, thank you. Please stay by my side from now on too!
大好きだよ！
I love you!
世界で一番お姫様。
The number one princess in the world.
そういう扱い心得てよね。
Make sure you know how to treat me as such.
よね！
Right!
みんなー！今日のライブ盛り上がってるのらー！
Everyone! Today's live is getting exciting, nora!
ルーナの可愛い歌声を聴いてほしいのらー！
I want you to listen to Luna's cute singing voice, nora!
その一、いつもと違う髪形に気がつくこと。
Number one, notice when my hairstyle is different from usual.
その二、ちゃんと靴まで見ること。いいね？
Number circle (two), look properly down to my shoes. Got it?
その三、私の一言には三つの言葉で返事すること。
Number three, reply to my every word with three words.
わかったら右手がお留守なのを何とかして！
If you understand, do something about my empty right hand!
別にわがままなんて言ってないんだから。
It's not like I'm being selfish or anything.
でも君に、心から思ってほしいの。可愛いって。
But I want you to think it from the bottom of your heart. That I'm cute.
世界で一番お姫様。
The number one princess in the world.
...ませ また溢れちゃうわ
...please. It's going to overflow again.
ありがとうと思ってないの
I'm not thinking "thank you."
甘いもの食べてみたい
I want to try eating something sweet.
ワン、ツー
One, two.
1つ
Number one:
可愛いの間違いでしょ
You mistake me for being cute, right?
文句は許しませんの
I won't allow any complaints.
あのね 私の話 ちゃんと聞いてて
Hey, listen to what I'm saying.
あ、それとね 白いお馬さん 決まってるでしょ
Oh, and also, the white horse is decided, right?
お迎えに来て
Come and pick me up.
わかったら かしづいて 手をとって「お姫様」って
If you understand, kneel, take my hand, and call me "Princess."
別に 我儘なんて 言ってないんだから
It's not like I'm being selfish or anything.
でもね 少し位 しかってくれてもいいのよ
But you know, it's okay to scold me a little.
世界で 私だけの 王子様
You're my only Prince in the world.
気がついて ほらほら お手手があいてます
Notice me, look, look, my hand is empty.
無口で 怖そうな 王子様
You're a quiet and scary-looking Prince.
もう どうして！
Geez, why?!
気がついてよ 早く
Notice me already!
ぜったい きみは わかってない
You definitely don't understand.
わかってないわ
You just don't get it.
ちょっと待ってよ だって 私は
Wait a minute, after all, I'm...
世界で 一番 お姫様
The number one Princess in the world.
ちゃんと見ててよね どこかに行っちゃうよ？
Keep your eyes on me, or I'll go somewhere else, you know?
ふいに 抱きしめられた 急に そんな ええ？！
Suddenly I was hugged, so out of the blue, what?!
「轢かれる あぶないよ」
"You'll get run over, it's dangerous."
そう言って そっぽ向く キミ
Saying that, you look away.
こっちのが あぶないわよ
This side is the dangerous one!
んなぁー！
Unnaaaa!
アー！！
Aaaah!!
皆さーん！
Everyone!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone!
みんなありがとうー！
ちょっと待って、こよりちゃん、こよりちゃん。
Wait a sec, Koyori-chan, Koyori-chan.
こよりちゃん、まだ自己紹介終わってないからね。
Koyori-chan, we haven't finished our self-introductions yet.
そっか、名乗らないとですね。
Oh right, we have to introduce ourselves.
そうですよ。じゃあ団長から名乗ります。
That's right. Then I'll start the introductions.
よろしくお願いします。
Please do.
はい！
Okay!
皆様、こんまっするー！
Everyone, Kon-muscle!
ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルと...
I'm Shirogane Noel from Hololive 3rd generation and...
はい！
Yes!
皆様、こんこよー！
Everyone, Kon-koyo!
ホロライブ6期生秘密結社holoXの、博衣こよりだよー！
I'm Hakui Koyori from Hololive 6th generation's Secret Society holoX!
はい皆様、hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade、いよいよ始まりましたー！
Okay everyone, hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade has finally begun!
始まりましたー！
It's begun!
あ、目が回った。
Ah, I'm dizzy.
大丈夫ですか？
Are you okay?
もう本当に緊張して。
Man, I'm just so nervous.
いや、そうだよね。だってこよりちゃん初めてじゃない、全体ライブ。
Yeah, I bet. After all, this is your first time in a full concert, isn't it?
全体ライブもだし、あとお客様がいるっていうのも初めてなんでもう...
It's my first full concert, and also the first time with an audience, so I'm...
まじか！
Seriously!
しかもね、声出しOKですからね。みんな声本当ありがとう！
And cheers are allowed! Everyone, thank you so much for your voices!
ありがとう！いっぱいありがとねー！
Thank you! Thank you so much!
幸せだー。
I'm so happy.
すごいね。
Incredible.
えーちょっと、ノエル先輩。
Um, excuse me, Noel-senpai.
こよりやりたいことあるんですけど。
There's something Koyori wants to do.
あるの？いいよ。
You have something? Sure.
悔いなく全部やっちゃえ。
Do it all without any regrets.
やっていいですか？
Can I?
やっ。
Yeah.
やっぱりね、声が出せるということで、
Well, you see, since we can hear your voices,
皆様もね、声出す練習もっともっとしないといけないと思うので。
I think everyone needs more practice using them.
コール＆レスポンス、していきませんかー！？
So, why don't we do a call and response!?
じゃあ、先輩お手本お願いします。
Then, Senpai, please show us an example.
任せて。
Leave it to me.
じゃあ、みんな！
Okay, everyone!
アリーナの人、声出して手を振れー！
People in the arena, let out your voices and wave your hands!
いいねー！最高。
Nice! Awesome.
それじゃあ。
And then...
2階席ー！イエーイ！
2nd floor seats! Yeah!
3階席ー！
The 3rd floor seats!
いいねー！
Nice!
いいよいいよー！
Great, great!
そして...
And...
そしてね、油断してる現地組だけかと思いきや...
Just when you might think it's only the venue group...
配信のみんなも見えてるよー！
We can see everyone on the stream too!
配信のみんなー！
Everyone on the stream!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ありがと、みんなも元気ですね！
Thank you, everyone is so energetic!
ナイス！
Nice!
あ、他もどうですか？
Oh, how about others too?
やりたい！うん！
I want to do it! Yeah!
じゃあ、いいですか？
Then, is it okay?
男の子ー、いますかー？
Are there any boys here?
男の子ー！
Boys!
いいねー！
Nice!
ナイス！
あ、じゃあ...
Ah, then...
女の子ー！
Girls!
えー、可愛い！いるよー！
Wow, so cute! They're here!
結構ね、あのカメラにも映ってましたからね、始まる前も。
Quite a few were on camera before we started.
確かに、嬉しい！
True, I'm so happy!
じゃあ、ちょっとこれも聞いとこう！
Then, let's ask this too!
どっちでもない人ー！
Anyone who is neither!
いるいる！
They're here!
いっぱいいる！
There are so many!
たくさんいた！
Lots of them!
じゃあ、えー、関東近郊から来たよって人ー！
Then, anyone who came from the Kanto area!
あー、やっぱ、多いですねー。
Ah, as expected, there are many.
でも、なんか挙げてない人もいるし...
But some people didn't raise their hands...
じゃあ、関東以外から来たよって人ー！
Then, people from outside Kanto!
遠くから！
From far away!
遠い日本！
From all over Japan!
すごい！遠くからありがと、ありがと！
Amazing! Thank you for coming from so far!
でも、そうだ、もっと遠く！
But, that's right, even further away!
海外ニキー！いますかー？
Are there any overseas guys?
OVERSEAS GUYS!
おおー！いるいる！
Oh! They're here!
すごーい！ありがとね！
Amazing! Thank you!
気をつけて帰ってね、まだ帰らないけど！
Get home safely! Not yet, though!
いやー、嬉しいですねー、すごいね！
Wow, I'm so happy! It's incredible!
じゃあ、ちょっと言葉も言ってもらいたいんですけど。
Then, I'd like you to say a few words too.
あ、いいですねー！
Oh, that's a great idea!
博衣の下の名前はなーに？
What is Hakui's given name?
いいねー！
Nice!
いいよ、嬉しい！
Good, I'm happy!
じゃあ、団長の名前はー？
Then, what is Danchou's name?
ナイス！
Nice!
朝ごはん何食べたー？
What did you eat for breakfast?
あ、ちょっと分からん！ごめんごめん！
Ah, I couldn't tell! Sorry, sorry!
いや、ちょっとさ、楽しすぎてさ、なんかずっとやりたいんだけど...
It's just so fun, I want to keep going...
けど、ちょっとね...
But, well...
まだまだあるぞということで、ちょっとね、お知らせです。
We still have more to go, so here's an announcement.
今回のハッシュタグ、皆さん覚えてますかー？
Does everyone remember the hashtag for this event?
ひろがるホロライブDAY1です！
It's #HirogaruHololiveDay1!
スクショとかもOKなので、いっぱいスクショとかツイートよろしくお願いします！
Screenshots are fine, so please tweet them a lot!
お願いします！
Please do!
そして一つだけ、残念なお知らせです。
And one piece of sad news.
YouTubeで無料チラ見せを見ている方は、ここまでとなります。
For those watching the free preview on YouTube, it ends here.
ここまでです！
This is it!
いやー、残念だ！もっと見たいよ、見たいよねー！
Aw, what a shame! I want to see more, don't you?
はい、見たいという方は、ぜひ概要欄から配信サイトに飛んでチケットのお買い求め、お願いいたします！
If you want to see more, please head to the link in the description to buy a ticket!
それでは、名残惜しいけど、行きますか！
It's sad to say goodbye, but shall we go?
じゃあ、この後も楽しんでくださいね！まだまだ続くよー！
Please enjoy the rest of the show! It's not over yet!
せーの！
Ready...
ひろがるホロライブー！
Hirogaru Hololive!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
The free part has ended!
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
The free segment has ended!
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
The free part of the broadcast has ended!
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!